James B. Murphy Papers ca.1918-1950 Mss.B.M956
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence, ca.1918-1950 (Box 1-39)
  - Robbins, Harry Pelham
  - Robbins, William Jacob
  - Roberts, Audrey
  - Roberts, Mildred
    - Wood, Francis C
  - Robertson, Albert D
    - Chapman, E H
    - World War I
  - Robertson, James J
  - Robinson, C S
    - World War I
  - Robinson, G Canby
  - Robinson, Harry P
  - Robinson, William S
  - Roche Organon Inc.
  - Rochester Academy of Medicine
    - Dean, William I
  - Rockefeller, David
  - Rockefeller, John D., Jr.
    - Dakin, H D
  - Rockefeller, Lawrence S
  - Rockefeller, Nelson
  - Rockefeller Foundation
    - Gregg, Alan
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr.
    - Wesep, H Van
    - Carter, W S
    - Sawyer, Wilbur A
    - O'Brien, Daniel P
  - Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
    - Holt, L Emmett
    - Blake, Francis G
    - James, Henry, Jr.
  - Rockefeller Institute - Applications and Recommendations
    - Murphy, Douglas P
    - Kopas, Joseph
    - Bueno, Humbert L
    - Bacon, Raymond F
    - Pauli, Ruth H
    - Rafferty, James A
    - Fitzgerald, Anne
    - Fieler, A H
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Hussey, R G
    - D'Amico, Joseph
    - Clarke, Harry
    - Morton, John J
    - Black, Maud E
    - Krasso, Ilona
    - Riter, E R
    - Pardee, Katherine
    - Bullen, B C
    - Longcope, Warfield T
    - Jack, William D
    - Apor, Emil
    - Morton, John J
    - Taylor, H D
    - Thayer, W S
    - Millet, John A P
    - Mara, James
    - Heiser, Victor George
    - Witherbee, W D
    - Chaulmley-Jones, Richard
    - Appleton, Mrs. Mary F
  - Rockefeller Institute Materials - History
    - Smith, Edric B
    - Prudden, T M
  - Rockefeller Institute - Reports
    - Gasser, Herbert
  - Roffo, C
  - Rogers, J B
  - Rohrer, C W G
  - Roos, Allan J
  - Roosevelt, Archibald B., Jr.
  - Rosahn, Paul D
  - Roscoe-Jackson Memorial Laboratory
  - Rosenfeld, G L
  - Rosenstirn, Julius
  - Rosenthal, Otto
  - Ross, Otho B
  - Rostenberg, Adolph
  - Rotenone, Etc. Notes - Misc.
  - Roumania. Consul
  - Rounsavell, R A
  - Rous, Peyton
    - World War I
  - Rowntree, L G
  - Royo Villanova, Dr.
  - Runnells, Russell A
  - Rusch, Harold R
  - Russ, Sidney
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Rollier
  - Russell, Charles D
  - Russell, Frederick F
    - Cunningham, John Sumter
  - Russell, Ruth B
  - Ryder, Charles T
  - Sabin, Albert B
  - Sabin, Florence Rena
    - Criscitiello, M
    - Belmont, Mrs. August
  - Saborido, J
  - Sachs, Fritz
  - Saint-George, Armin V
    - Rous, Peyton
  - Salter, William T
  - Sanchez, Victor Adan
  - Sanderson, Raymond
  - Sanderson, S E
  - Santiago, Oliver H
  - Sargent, Mrs. Amy
  - Sargent, Thornton W
  - Sater, Clifford
  - Sawyer, Wilbur A
    - X-Ray
  - Saxl, Erwin J
  - Schaefer, A, Jr.
  - Scaife, Marvin F
  - Schaughnessey, H L
  - Scheider, Alfred M
  - Schereschewsky, J W
  - Schilling, George S
  - Schling, Max
  - Schlitz, Frances H
  - Schneider, Herbert W
  - Schneider, J
  - Schober, Bruno
    - Mider, G B
    - Payne, George C
  - Schram, Mildred W S
    - Woglom, William H
    - Potter, Van R
    - Haven, Frances L
    - Bayne-Jones, S
    - Schrek, Robert
  - Schrek, Robert
    - Machlan, H F
  - Schroeder, Lloyd H
  - Schultz, Edwin
  - Schwab, Mrs. Madeleine F
  - Schwartz, James B
  - Schwenck, Erwin
  - Schwenter, Victor
  - Science
    - Valentine, Willard L
    - Cattell, J McKeen
  - Science Press
  - Science Service
    - Davis, Watson
    - Cattell, J McKeen
  - Scott, A C
  - Scott, Mrs. J Virgil
  - Scott, W J Merle
  - Seal Harbor, Maine
  - Seeing Eye
    - Clark, Mrs. Dorothy Q P
  - Seibert, Mrs. J P
    - Murray, Harold A
  - Sellards, Andrew Watson
  - Semken, George H
  - Sennet
  - Seton, Mrs. Alfred
  - Seybolt, John F
  - Seymour, George W
  - Shattuck, Howard F
  - Shelton, Elbert M
  - Shipley, P G
  - Shippen, Mrs. Florence
  - Shohan, Joseph
  - Shope, Richard E
  - Shrigley, E W
  - Shull, George H
  - Silvercruys, Robert
  - Simmons, Bruce
  - Simonds, J P
    - World War I
  - Simons, George N
  - Simpson, B T
  - Simpson, W O
    - O'Dwyer, William
  - Simpson, William L
  - Simunek, Jerry Anton
  - Singer
  - Skapier, Joseph
  - Skinner, Edward H
  - Skipper, Howard E
    - Rhoads, C P
  - Slemons, J Morris
  - Sloan, Alfred P., Jr.
  - Sloan, Elizabeth
  - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research
    - Rhoads, C P
    - Hess, H Lawrence
    - Sloan, Alfred P., Jr.
  - Slocum, C Jonathan
  - Smith, Augustine J
  - Smith, Edric B
    - World War I
    - Flexner, Simon
    - James, Henry, Jr.
    - Risley, D E
    - Life Photographic Exhibitions
  - Smith, George A
  - Smith, George M
  - Smith, Horace E
  - Smith, Hugh H
  - Smith, Ismael
  - Smith, Jain MacLean
  - Smith, Theobald
  - Smith, William E
  - Smith, Winifred
  - Smith, Kline & French Laboratories
    - Boyer, Francis
    - Shanley, M C
  - Smithline, Jacob
  - Smyth, Charles J
  - Snell, George D
  - Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine
    - Goldfarb, A J
  - Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine. Proceedings.
    - Goldfarb, A J
  - Society of Cellular Biology
  - Sokoloff, Boris
  - Solomons, Bethel
  - Sordelli, A
  - Spencer, Herta
  - Spencer, R R
  - Spies, Charles B
  - Spies, John W
    - Van Allen
    - Galpin, Perrin C
  - Springer, Stewart
    - Porter, K R
  - Spiro, Mrs. George
  - Sprofkin, Bertram E
  - Sproul, Alexander Erskine
  - Sprunt, Douglas H
  - Spur (Magazine)
  - Staley, Marie E
  - Stander, Henricus J
  - Stanley, A W
  - State Institute for the Study of Malignant Disease
    - Simpson, Burton T
  - Stebbins, G Ledyard
  - Stebbins, Henry D
  - Stein, Gertrude
  - Steiner, Paul
    - Rhoads, C P
    - Harrison, R W
    - Owen, Philip S
  - Stelling, Mrs. Charlotte J
    - Stelling, Edna
    - Reynolds, H C
  - Stephenson
  - Stephenson, C S
    - New York Times
  - Sternsland, Gurine
    - Clayland, J M
    - Root, Clark, Buckner & Howland
    - Ravn, C N
  - Stetson, Richard P
  - Stevens, Kenneth P
  - Stevens, R L., Jr.
  - Stevens, Rollin H
  - Stewart, Florence M
  - Stewart, Fred W
    - Wadsworth, Augustus B
    - Marsh, Millard C
  - Stewart, Harold J
  - Stewart, Maxwell S
  - Stewart, Thomas M
  - Stewart, William R
  - Stitt, Edward Rhodes
    - World War I
  - Stockard, Charles L
  - Stone, William S
  - Storey, Charles M., Jr.
  - Storey, W Edward
  - Storrow, James C
    - Storrow, Edward C
  - Stout, Arthur Purdy
  - Stowell, Robert E
  - Strickler, Albert
  - Strode, George K
  - Strong, Leonell C
    - American College Bureau
    - Fisk Teachers Agency
    - Palmer, Waller W
    - Gay, Frederick P
    - Wilson, Louis B
    - Smith, Edric B
    - Corwin, Margaret T
    - Palmer, W W
    - Fish, H D
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Strong, Richard P
  - Strycker, P J De
  - Sturm, Ernest
  - Subjects for Lectures by Different People
  - Sugiura, Kanematsu
  - Sulzberger, Arthur Hays
  - Sulzberger, Mrs. Iphigene Ochs
  - Sulzberger, Judy
  - Sumner, James B
  - Sweeney, Thomas Bell
  - Symeonidis, A
    - Schram, Mildred
    - Spencer, R P
  - Table Talk: Century Magazine, April 1929
  - Talley, W W
    - X-Ray
  - Tannenbaum, Albert
  - Tanzer, Radford C
  - Tar Method
    - Newburger, Bernhard
  - Tata Memorial Hospital
  - Taussig, Fred J
  - Taylor, Elizabeth
  - Taylor, G C
  - Taylor, Herbert D
    - World War I
  - Taylor, Howard C
  - Taylor, Isaac M
    - World War I
  - Taylor, Kenneth
    - World War I
  - Taylor, R M
  - Teaham, Roscoe W
  - Tejada Valenzuela, Carlos
  - TenBroeck, Carl
  - Tesar, Charles
    - Sherman, Henry C
    - Hayden, Philip M
    - Jackson, Richard W
  - Teter, E A
  - Thannhauser, S J
  - Thayer, Mrs. John B
  - Thayer, W S
  - Thiel, Martin A
    - Hartman, Howard R
    - McGavran, Charles W
  - Thomas, Arthur H., Co.
  - Thomas, M
    - World War I
  - Thompson, Blanche
  - Thompson, J W
  - Thompson, L R
  - Thorndike, Augustus
    - Paine, Charles F
    - Campbell Mfg. Co.
    - Hanovia Chemical & Mfg. Co.
  - Thornton, John J
  - Tibbets, Albert P
  - Tidmarsh, Clarence
  - Tiffany, H E
  - Time (Magazine)
  - Tobey, James A
  - Tod, Margaret C
  - Tomarkin
  - Tone, Aileen
  - Tonsil Records
    - Vermilge, H N
    - Witherbee, W
  - Tonsil X-Ray
  - Tonsils
    - Osgood, Herman A
    - O'Shaughnessy, E J
    - Crowe, Samuel J
    - Whipple, George H
    - Witherbee, W D
    - Bordley, James
    - Baetjer, F H
    - Hickey, P M
    - Young, R G
    - Brown, Robert O
    - Wilson, B C
    - Beyer, David S
    - Nichols, H J
    - Craig, Charles F
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Yates, J L
    - Robb, J M
    - Murphy, J
    - Angell, James R
    - Amoss, Harold L
    - Whitney, W R
    - Crumbaugh, J W
  - Tonsils and Adenoids
  - Town and Country
    - Bull, Harry
  - Townsend, Arthur
  - Townsend, M L
  - Traeger's Tropicals
  - Trager, William
  - Train, Arthur
    - Stewart, Fred W
  - Traut, H F
    - Stander, H J
    - Schiefflin, William J
  - Trowbridge, Mrs.
    - Sullivan
    - Mathews, Frank S
  - Trudeau, E L
  - Trussel, Wilbur E
  - Tuttle, George T
  - Tuve, M A
  - Twins, Identical, References.
  - Twombly, Gray H
  - Tyson, Michel
  - Uhlmann, Erich
    - Holfelder, Hans
    - Herxheimer, Karl
    - Aub, Joseph
  - Uhma, Chester
    - Zubrzycki, J
  - Uhma, Czeslaw
    - Cullen, Thomas S
    - Morton, John J
    - Aub, Joseph
    - Reimann, Stanley P
    - MacCallum, William G
    - Zubrzycki, January
  - Underhill, Eugene
  - Union Internationale Contre Le Cancer
    - Godart, Justin
    - Straus, Jesse I
    - Bandaline, J
    - Wood, Francis Carter
    - Little, C C
    - Ewing, James
    - Reding
    - Maisin, J
    - Schraenen, M W
    - Lerat
    - Claude, Albert
  - L'Union Medicale Du Canada
    - LeSage, Albert
  - U.S. Army Records
  - United States Government Cancer Control.
    - Gasser, Herbert S
    - Hektoen, Ludvig
    - Parran, Thomas
    - Thompson, L R
  - United States Public Health Cancer Committee
    - Jones, Wesley L
    - Cumming, H S
    - Bloodgood, Joseph Colt
    - Pierce, C C
    - Draper, W F
    - Wood, Francis Carter
    - Stimson, A M
  - U.S. Surgeon General's Office
    - Stotesbury, Louis W
    - World War I
  - U.S. War Dept. - Adjutant General's Office
    - World War I
  - U.S. War Dept. - Zone Finance Office
    - World War I
  - University of North Carolina
    - Berryhill, W R
    - Odum, Howard W
    - Saunders, J Maryon
    - Venable, Francis P
    - Chase, H W
  - University of North Carolina. Sesquicentennial Celebration
    - Grumman, Russell M
    - Wilson, Louis R
  - University of Pennsylvania
  - University of Pennsylvania Cancer Committee
    - Brakeley, George A
    - Meeker, G H
    - McDonald, Ellice
    - Ewing, James
    - Kern, Richard
  - University of Texas
  - University of Wisconsin
    - Bardeen, C R
    - Stovall, W D
    - Crownhart, J G
    - Wilson, Louis B
    - Taylor, J Gurney
    - Middleton, William S
    - Johnson, James
    - Appel, Livia
  - Unknown
  - Upjohn, E Gifford, Jr.
    - Upjohn Company
    - MacLeod, A Gerrard
    - Morris, Stanley
  - Uruguay, Consul, New York
  - Vaccination Data
  - Valaitis, Jonas
    - Letterer, E
  - Van Allen, C M
  - Vanamee, Parker
    - Fulton, Frank T
    - Means, J H
    - Castle, W B
    - Joyce, Henry S
    - Thorne, George W
    - Chambers, William H
  - VanAnda, George H
  - Van Der Schueren, Gerard
    - Andervont, H B
    - Aub, Joseph
    - Ortel, Horst
    - McEwen, C S
    - Galpin, Pierre C
    - Slye, Maud
    - Evans, Herbert
    - Banting, F G
    - Burrows, Montrose
    - Cutler, Max
    - Morton, John J
    - McDonald, Ellice
    - Geschickter, Charles F
    - Bloodgood, Joseph Colt
    - Lewis, Warren H
    - Reimann, Stanley P
  - Von Der Osten, Anna L
  - Van Es, L
  - Van Kley, L A
    - Duffy, Benedict J
  - Van Slyke, Donald D
    - Hufferd, Ralph W
    - World War I
  - Van Waeyenbergh, H
  - Venable, Francis P
  - Vernon, James W
    - Gregg, Alan
  - Vincent, George E
  - Vita Glass Corporation
  - Voegtlin, Carl
  - Voorhis, Anna Harvey
  - Wachtel, Joseph S
  - Wade, Nelson J
  - Wadsworth, Augustus B
  - Wagner, Carla
  - Wah Wahoo, A J
  - Wainwright, Charles W
  - Wainwright, J M
  - Waite and Bartlett Mfg. Co.
  - Waksman
  - Walker, Mrs. A Stewart
  - Walker, George
  - Walker, Sir James
  - Wallace, George B
  - Walsh, J F
  - Walsh, Mrs. J F
  - Walton, A J
  - Wampole, Frank
  - Wang, Chengting T
  - Wanger, Justine
  - Warburg, Otto
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Warburton, Gladys
  - Ward, Gordon R
  - Ward, Lewis H
  - Ward, S I
  - Warden, Mrs. Clarence A
  - Waring, James J
  - Warner, Jack
  - Warner, Grace M
    - Russell, Mary A
    - Sturm, Ernest
  - Warner, M G
  - Warren, Shields
    - Morris, Harold P
  - Warren, Stafford L
  - Warthin, A S
    - World War I
  - Washington Post
  - Washington University
  - Wasteney, Hardolph
  - Waters, Nelson F
  - Waterson, Davina
  - Watkins, F B
  - Watkins, W Warner
  - Watson, David L
  - Watson, George F
  - Webb, Gerald B
  - Webster, Leslie Tillotson
  - Weed, Lewis H
    - Corner, George W
  - Weil, Charles L
  - Weil, Richard
  - Weinberg, C Berenda
  - Weintraub, D
  - Weintraub, A D
    - Kolmer, John A
  - Weintraub, Solomon
  - Weir, Mrs. Margaret Bronson
    - X-Ray
    - Pillsbury, Donald
    - Roberts, Frederick W
  - Welch, William Henry
    - Coley, William B
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Welker, W H
  - Wells, Clifford W
  - Wells, H Gideon
  - Welsh, John D
  - Wendling, Edward J
  - Wendt, Gerald L
    - Mory, A V H
  - Werner, Mrs. Lillian B
  - Wesson, Miley B
  - West, Thornton
  - Whaley, G P
  - Whipple, Allen O
  - Whipple, George H
  - Whitaker, Douglas
    - Heath, Harold
  - Whitaker, L A
  - White, James T., and Co.
  - White, Philip R
  - White, W Elliott
    - Palmer, W W
    - White, Mrs. Addis
  - White, William Crawford
    - Lee, Burton J
  - Whitehead, R H
  - Whitmore, W S
  - Whittemore, Thomas
  - Whitty, M J
    - Ordway, Thomas
    - DuBois, Eugene F
    - Whitty, A
    - Mooney, P H
  - Who's Who
  - Wickenden, Homer
    - Mason, Max
    - Fisher, Henry J
    - Greef, J G
  - Wiegand, W B
  - Wiesner, Mrs. Dora
    - Hutchinson, Robert H., Jr.
    - Wiesner, Lillian
  - Wilchinski, Martha L
    - World War I
  - Wiley, Louis
  - Williams, Charles J
  - Williams, Francis H
  - Williams, L B
    - X-Ray
  - Williams, Mary Lydia
  - Williams, Robert
    - Craver, Lloyd F
  - Wilmarding, Lucius
  - Wilmer, William H
  - Wilson, Edwin B
  - Wilson, George W
  - Wilson, H V
  - Wilson, Mrs. J
    - Clark, Peter S
  - Windley, William Hays
    - Ferrell, John A
    - Lewis, Kemp P
  - Wink, H B
  - Winslow, C E A
  - Winter, Norman
  - Winternitz, Milton C
  - Winters, Mary E
  - Winton, Berley
  - Wishoian
  - Wistar Institute of Anatomy and Biology
  - Witherbee, W D
    - World War I
  - Witherbee, W D. A Preliminary Study of the Effects of Ultra Violet Light Upon Pneumocci and Streptocci.
  - Withers, Sanford
  - Woerdeman, M W
  - Woglom, William H
  - Woglom, William H
    - Wells, H Gideon
  - Wolbach, S B
  - Wolf, Ralph R
  - Women's Medical College
  - Wood, Francis Carter
    - Little, C C
    - Charlton, H E W
  - Wood, H E
  - Woods, Alexander Hamilton
  - Woods, Archie S
  - Woods, Arthur
  - Woods, Edward A
  - Woods, Mrs. Helen
  - Woods, John P
  - Woods, Leonard
  - Woodward, Alvalyn E
  - Woolley, Eola Claire
  - Worthington, Mrs. Mary Spencer
    - World War I
  - Wright, Arthur W
  - Wright, Isaac C
  - Wright, R Douglas
  - Wright and Hirschberg
  - Wrinch, Dorothy M
  - Wyckoff, Polly
  - Wyeth, George A
  - Yates, J L
  - Yeaton, Edward E
  - Ycaza, C R De
  - Young, Anderson G
  - Young, R G
  - Yugoslavia Embassy
  - Zabriskie, Edwin G
  - Zaletal, R P
  - Zerfas, L G
  - Zinsser, Hans
  - Zoological Research Supply
  - Zueblin, Ernest